var quiz = [

{
	"question" : "FYI",
	"correctanswer": "FOR YOUR INFORMATION",
	"answer2": "FORGET YOU IDIOT",
	"answer3": "FOR YOUR INSPECTION",
	"answer4": "FOR YOUR INBOX",

},

{

	"question" : "OMG",
	"correctanswer": "OH MY GOD",
	"answer2": "OOF MY GRADE",
	"answer3": "OMEGA",
	"answer4": "OH MY GOODNESS",
},

{

	"question" : "SMH",
	"correctanswer": "SHAKE MY HEAD",
	"answer2": "STOP MAKING HUMMUS",
	"answer3": "SO MUCH HATE",
	"answer4": "SCRATCHING MY HEAD",
},

{

	"question" : "TBH",
	"correctanswer": "TO BE HONEST",
	"answer2": "THE BEST HUSBAND",
	"answer3": "TO BE HATED",
	"answer4": "TOTAL BODY HUG",
},

{

	"question" : "LMK",
	"correctanswer": "LET ME KNOW",
	"answer2": "LET MIKE KNOW",
	"answer3": "TELL ME",
	"answer4": "LOSER MANAGE KETCHUP",
},

{

	"question" : "NVM",
	"correctanswer": "NEVERMIND",
	"answer2": "NOT VERY MUCH",
	"answer3": "NATIONAL VOLCANIC MONUMENT",
	"answer4": "NOT VERY MATURE",
},

{

	"question" : "ILY",
	"correctanswer": "I LOVE YOU",
	"answer2": "I LIKE YOU",
	"answer3": "I'M LEAVING YOU",
	"answer4": "I LOATHE YOU",
},

{

	"question" : "WTF",
	"correctanswer": "WHAT THE FUCK",
	"answer2": "WHY THE FACE?",
	"answer3": "WHAT THE FRUITCAKE",
	"answer4": "WHERE'S THE FUN",
},

{

	"question" : "LOL",
	"correctanswer": "LAUGH OUT LOUD",
	"answer2": "LOTS OF LOVE",
	"answer3": "LAP OF LUXURY",
	"answer4": "LITTLE OLD LADY",
},

{

	"question" : "OMW",
	"correctanswer": "ON MY WAY",
	"answer2": "ONE MINUTE WONDER",
	"answer3": "ON MY WAFFLE",
	"answer4": "OBERBAUMESSAGEN",
},

{

	"question" : "IRL",
	"correctanswer": "IN REAL LIFE",
	"answer2": "ONE MINUTE WONDER",
	"answer3": "ON MY WAFFLE",
	"answer4": "OBERBAUMESSAGEN",
},


]


















